[
    {
        "question": "It can be inferred from the passage that the Countess of Huntingdon",
        "options": [
            "didn't care about Phillis‘ poetry",
            "helped Phillis get her writings published",
            "believed in slavery",
            "was surprised that Phillis could read and write"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What question is answered in last paragraph?",
        "options": [
            "Who did Phillis marry?",
            "Where were Phillis‘ works published?",
            "What did Phillis prove?",
            "Why was Phillis a slave?"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillis finally became free .............",
        "options": [
            "when she published her-poems in England",
            "after meeting the Countess of Huntingdon",
            "when she became wealthy",
            "after her master died"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillis‘ first attempt at selling her poetry in America (the colonies) was .................",
        "options": ["illegal", "imaginary", "unsuccessful", "successful"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is TRUE about Phillis Wheatley?",
        "options": [
            "She was the first African-American slave to visit England.",
            "She was the first African-American and slave to publish a book in the United States.",
            "She was the first African-American and slave to be able to read and write",
            "She was the first African-American and slave to meet George Washington."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wheatley family estimated the age of the slave girl they named “Phills\" by",
        "options": [
            "her size",
            "the condition of her teeth",
            "her color",
            "her weight"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "By the age of twelve, Phillis was ...................",
        "options": [
            "no longer a slave",
            "married",
            "a published poet",
            "still not able to read or write"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The slaveowner who sold Phillis to the Wheatley family believed ...............",
        "options": [
            "she would soon recover from her illness",
            "she was very intelligent",
            "she was worth a lot of money",
            "she would soon die"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was George Whiteﬁeld?",
        "options": [
            "A military general",
            "Somebody who Phillis admired greatly",
            "Phillis‘ husband",
            "A slave owner"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Phillis Wheatley buried?",
        "options": ["No one knows", "Africa", "Boston", "Virginia"],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    }
]
